# **RAMCES GIL**

1107 East 229th Street, Apartment 2C Bronx, New York 10466 (518) 888-1501 Ramces2580@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ramces-gil

### **SUMMARY**

A talented and performance-driven software engineer, with extensive education and experience in web development, JavaScript and other JavaScript libraries such as React. Additional strengths in cybersecurity. A skilled and reliable worker, who demonstrates established capabilities in time management and multitasking to improve overall efficiency. Builds team efficiency and morale through usage of exemplary leadership and communication skills.

## **EXPERIENCE**

JETBLACK, New York, New York **Dispatcher**, 2018-2020

- Supervised small team of procurement specialists to ensure all deliveries arrived on time.
- Ensured problem deliveries were addressed and delivered on schedule.
- Organized and prepared daily tasks for procurement specialists, and strategized stores from which procurement specialists bought items and made deliveries.

## Fulfillment Specialist, 2018-2019

- Improved quality check process flow from four-step process to three-step process, ensuring efficiency on customer deliveries.
- Organized shipments for daily delivery and executed quality control on all deliveries.
- Redesigned warehouse to accommodate growing customer base demand.
- Created Excel sheets to ensure accurate inventory count.

UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES, Albany, New York

Senior Student Assistant, 2014-2018

- Provided student services to the entire university community of 18,000 faculty, staff, and students.
- Adhered to SUNY and New York State policies and guidelines.
- Processed cash transactions.
- Reorganized shelf space in order to fit new inventory and make shelving more efficient.

# **EDUCATION**

SUNY UNIVERSITY AT ALBANY, Albany, New York, B.S., Informatics, Concentration in Cybersecurity, Minor in Criminal Justice, 2018

Team Treehouse April 2020

### **Techdegree Certification in Front-End Development**

 Course Work: JavaScript and the DOM, Object-Oriented JavaScript, Callback Functions in JavaScript, Ajax Basics, Asynchronous Programming with JavaScript, JavaScript Array Iteration Methods

## LEADERSHIP ACTIVITIES

Educational Opportunity Program, Student Assistant, Senior Academic Advisor Claudio Gomez, 2018 Chinese Student Association, Public Relations Chair, 2017

### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

Microsoft Office, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React